<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PackBagBuddy-Leisure, Travel and Tourism</string>

    <string name="adventure_trip">Adventure Trips</string>
    <string name="popularSport">Popular Sports</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment 2</string>
    <string name="kasol_Trek">Popular as ‘Mini Israel’ in the beautiful state of Himachal Pradesh, Kasol is a quaint hamlet positioned at a height of 1,640 m along the banks of River Parvati. It is located at a distance of 37 km from Kullu and lies between Bhuntur and Manikaran. The site offers picturesque views of Parvati Valley and snow-capped mountains. There is an old swinging bridge which divides Kasol into Old Kasol and New Kasol.

Blessed with the abundance of flora and fauna, milky waterfalls, delectable delicacies and friendly locals, Kasol has become a famous tourist destination for bag packers, trekkers and nature lovers. Not only Indian travellers, even foreigners can be seen in Kasol, especially young Israelis. Thus, it is one of the best places to spend a vacation in the lap of nature with everlasting exquisiteness.

With perfect weather and temperature, Kasol is a year-round destination for tourists. However, most of the people prefer to visit it during the summer season from April to June. Moreover, it is an apt time for adventure enthusiasts as most of the trekking routes become accessible by this time. And notably, Kasol serves as the base camp for many treks. Nature and wildlife photographers travel to discover the hidden gems of this place in winters as snow enhances its beauty.</string>
<string name="kareri_lake">Kareri Lake Trek is located at an elevation of about 2,950 meters in Kangra district of Himachal Pradesh. It is a perfect weekend getaway if you want to switch off from your monotonous routine and get close to nature.

Surrounded by mountains and alpine trees, the Kareri Lake Trek is formed by the flow of the water bodies from by the Minkiani peak. The trek to Kareri Lake Trek is one of the most scenic alpine treks in Himachal Pradesh that goes to several gushing streams and passes through green meadows. You will come across artistic shepherd villages that have a charm of their own. Other attractions are the Lord Shiva temple which is worth a visit. The trail to Kareri Lake Trek will definitely interest you if you\'re interested in bird watching as there are various species of birds to look out for. So be ready with your cameras for that perfect capture. The forests here are a mix of pines and shrubs which act as a perfect hiding for some exclusive birds.</string>
<string name="kedarnath">Kedarnath is a holy Hindu town located in Rudraprayag district of Uttarakhand in India. It is one of the Char Dhams located in the Himalayas. Kedarnath is situated at an astonishing height of 3584 meters above sea level near the head of Mandakini River.

The Kedarnath temple lies amidst the majestic snow-capped Garhwal Himalayan ranges and is thronged by thousands of tourists each year</string>

</resources>